<script>
	<questions>

		<flow>
			<question id='1'/>
			<question id='2'/>
			<question id='3'/>
			<if id='1' response='A'>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.7]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.6]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.1]'/>
				<if id='profile.7' response='C,D'>
					<question id='4'/>
					<question id='5'/>					
					<question id='6'/>
					<if id='6' response='B'>					
						<condition id='[1].[profile.6].days_off'/>
					</if>
				</if>
				<question id='7'/>

			</if>
			<if id='1' response='C'>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.2]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.4]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.6]'/>
			</if>
			<if id='1' response='B'>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.2]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.3]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.4]'/>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.5]'/>
				<screen id='phq2'/>
			</if>
			<if id='1' response='D'>
				<condition id='[1].[profile.6]'/>
				<screen id='stop'/>
				<screen id='phq2'/>
			</if>
			<if id='1' response='E'>
				<question id='8'/>
			</if>
			<if id='1' response='F'>
				<question id='9'/>
				<if id='9' response='A'>
					<question id='10'/>
				</if>
			</if>
		</flow>

		<question id='1'>
			<prompt>What is the biggest problem when exercising?</prompt>
			<option id='A' condition='time'>I don't have time to exercise</option>
			<option id='B' condition='motivation'>I find it hard to get started</option>
			<option id='C' condition='boredom'>I get bored while exercising</option>
			<option id='D' condition='tired'>I am too tired to exercise</option>
			<option id='E' condition='weather'>The weather gets in the way of exercising</option>
			<option id='F' condition='injury'>I have an injury that prevents me from exercising</option>
		</question>

		<question id='2'>
			<prompt>When do you usually go to bed?</prompt>
			<time/>
		</question>

		<question id='3'>
			<prompt>When do you usually get up?</prompt>
			<time/>
		</question>

		<question id='4'>
			<prompt>What time do you leave for work/school?</prompt>
			<time/>
		</question>

		<question id='5'>
			<prompt>What time do you get home from work/school?</prompt>
			<time/>
		</question>		

		<question id='6'>
			<prompt>How many days a week do you have off from work and school?</prompt>
			<option id='A'>None</option>
			<option id='B'>1 or more</option>
		</question>
		<question id='7'>
			<prompt>How many days a week are you exercising for 15 minutes or more at a time?</prompt>
			<option id='A'>1</option>
			<option id='B'>2</option>
			<option id='C'>3</option>
			<option id='D'>4</option>
			<option id='E'>5</option>
			<option id='F'>6</option>
			<option id='G'>7</option>
		</question>

		<question id='8'>
			<prompt>Which weather conditions are causing you to cancel you workouts lately?</prompt>
			<option id='A' condition='weather.hot'>Hot</option>
			<option id='B' condition='weather.cold'>Cold</option>
			<option id='C' condition='weather.rain'>Rain</option>
			<option id='D' condition='weather.snow'>Snow</option>
		</question>

		<question id='9'>
			<prompt>Do you have a physical therapist?</prompt>
			<option id='A' condition='injury.has_therapist'>Yes</option>
			<option id='B' condition='injury.no_therapist'>No</option>
		</question>

		<question id='10'>
			<prompt>Have you already consulted your physical therapist about your injury?</prompt>
			<option id='A' condition='injury.has_therapist.visited'>Yes</option>
			<option id='B' condition='injury.has_therapist.not_visited'>No</option>
		</question>



	</questions>

	<conditions>
		<condition name='time'>58,53,77,46,42</condition>
			<condition name='time.profile.7.work_student'>1,70</condition>
			<condition name='time.profile.7.work_student'>1,70</condition>			
			<condition name='time.profile.7.work.days_off'>68,49</condition>
			<condition name='time.profile.7.student.days_off'>68,49</condition>
			<condition name='time.profile.7.homemaker'>36</condition>

			<condition name='time.profile.6.children'>57,39,27,13,4,16</condition>


		<condition name='motivation'>47,41,77,25,60,58,63,79,75</condition>
			<condition name='motivation.profile.2.alone'>11,54</condition>
			<condition name='motivation.profile.2.friend'>92,48,81,15,55</condition>
			<condition name='motivation.profile.2.trainer'>50,67,90,82</condition>
			<condition name='motivation.profile.2.group'>50,67,90,82</condition>
			<condition name='motivation.profile.2.any'>11,50,67,90,92,48,15,91</condition>

		<condition name='boredom'></condition>
		<condition name='boredom.profile.2.alone'>45,21,52,28,9,88,34,37,93,74</condition>
		<condition name='boredom.profile.2.friend'>9,59,38,73,56,10,3</condition>
		<condition name='boredom.profile.2.trainer'>17,2,38,19,20</condition>
		<condition name='boredom.profile.2.any'>45,21,52,28,9,88,34,37,93,74,9,59,73,56,10,3,17,2,38,19,20</condition>
		<condition name='boredom.profile.children'>57,39,16</condition>

		<condition name='tired'></condition>
		<condition name='tired.profile.children'>7,57,39,16,83</condition>

		<condition name='weather'>24,94,18,26</condition>
			<condition name='weather.hot'>101</condition>
			<condition name='weather.cold'>33</condition>
			<condition name='weather.rain'>32</condition>
			<condition name='weather.snow'>31,72</condition>

		<condition name='injury'></condition>
			<condition name='injury.has_therapist'>6</condition>
				<condition name='injury.has_therapist.visited'>86,22,97</condition>
				<condition name='injury.has_therapist.not_visited'>6,69</condition>
			<condition name='injury.no_therapist'>86,51</condition>
	</conditions>

	<solutions>
		<solution id='1'>Ask a coworker or friend to walk during your lunch break.</solution>
		<solution id='2'>Ask a fit friend to help you design a beginner exercise program. </solution>
		<solution id='3'>Ask a friend or family member who doesn't want to exercise with you to keep you company while you exercise at home. </solution>
		<solution id='4'>Ask spouse to help with childcare at times you would like to exercise</solution>
		<solution id='5'>Ask your doctor to be tested for sleep apnea</solution>
		<solution id='6'>Ask your PT to develop an exercise plan for you that will not cause pain and help your injury heal. </solution>
		<solution id='7'>Ask your spouse to watch children during your exercise time and do the same for him/her/</solution>
		<solution id='8'>Between [time] and [time] you could plan some physical activity.</solution>
		<solution id='9'>Chat with a friend on the phone while you workout.</solution>
		<solution id='10'>Connect with friends on fitness mobile apps so you can motivate each other.</solution>
		<solution id='11'>Download an app to track your exercise (e.g., MapMyWalk, Fitbit)</solution>
		<solution id='12'>Eliminate caffiene after noon.</solution>
		<solution id='13'>Exercise after your child goes to bed at night or while they are napping</solution>
		<solution id='14'>Extend the length of your workout by 5 mins.</solution>
		<solution id='15'>Find a buddy to report your exercise to each week, and he/she will do the same to you for accountability</solution>
		<solution id='16'>Find a gym that has childcare</solution>
		<solution id='17'>Find a gym that offers personal training services.</solution>
		<solution id='18'>Find a local gym you feel comfortable with.</solution>
		<solution id='19'>Find a mobile app that offers personal training.</solution>
		<solution id='20'>Find a personal trainer who does online personal training.</solution>
		<solution id='21'>Find a TV series on Netflix that you will only watch during workouts.</solution>
		<solution id='22'>Find an exercise that does not cause pain to the injured area (e.g., upper body exercises if injury is in knee)</solution>
		<solution id='23'>Find an outdoor swimming pool you can use for your workouts.</solution>
		<solution id='24'>Find free exercise videos on Youtube that you can do indoors.</solution>
		<solution id='25'>Find some free exercise videos on Youtube </solution>
		<solution id='26'>Find used home exercise equipment on Craigslist.com</solution>
		<solution id='27'>Get a babysitter to watch your child while you exercise.</solution>
		<solution id='28'>Get a book or laptop holder for your treadmill or stationary bike</solution>
		<solution id='29'>Go to bed at the same time everyday.</solution>
		<solution id='30'>Go to sporting goods store and ask for hot weather exercise clothing.</solution>
		<solution id='31'>Go to sporting goods store and ask for thermal gear for outdoor exercise in cold conditions.</solution>
		<solution id='32'>Go to sporting goods store and ask for waterproof gear for outdoor exercise in wet conditions.</solution>
		<solution id='33'>Go to sporting goods store and ask for waterproof, thermal gear for outdoor exercise in cold conditions.</solution>
		<solution id='34'>Have three different workouts that you rotate throughout the week.</solution>
		<solution id='35'>Identify a source of stress that you can eliminate. </solution>
		<solution id='36'>Identify a stressful time consuming task that you can delegate to someone else to make time to exercise</solution>
		<solution id='37'>If you walk, bike or run outside, try a different route.</solution>
		<solution id='38'>If your friend is at a different exercise level, find ways to do different activities together (e.g., ride a bike alongside him/her while he/she runs).</solution>
		<solution id='39'>Incorporate active play with your child such as dancing,  active videogames, or nature hike</solution>
		<solution id='40'>Increase the intensity of the [exercise] to increase calories burned while reducing total exercise time.</solution>
		<solution id='41'>Join a Facebook group where people support and motivate each other about exercise</solution>
		<solution id='42'>Keep a journal of how you spend your time to identify where you might be able to fit in more exercise</solution>
		<solution id='43'>Keep a pair of sneakers at work so you are prepared to go for a walk</solution>
		<solution id='44'>Keep your room cool at night.</solution>
		<solution id='45'>Listen to an audiobook while exercising</solution>
		<solution id='46'>Make a list of reasons exercise is important to you. Post on the fridge.</solution>
		<solution id='47'>Make a list of the reasons you want to get fit and post on the refrigerator.</solution>
		<solution id='48'>Make a phone date with a friend during your walks.</solution>
		<solution id='49'>Make a plan to exercise on days you are not working (e.g., weekends)</solution>
		<solution id='50'>Make an appointment with a personal trainer</solution>
		<solution id='51'>Make an appointment with a physical therapist for help in developing a safe exercise regimen. </solution>
		<solution id='52'>Make an exercise playlist of your favorite high energy tunes.</solution>
		<solution id='53'>On some days, wake up earlier to exercise. Try going to bed earlier to make up the sleep.</solution>
		<solution id='54'>Plan a fun goal that will motivate you to start training  (e.g., climb a mountain, bike to a certain destination, etc)</solution>
		<solution id='55'>Plan a fun goal with a friend that will motivate you to start training  (e.g., climb a mountain, bike to a certain destination, etc)</solution>
		<solution id='56'>Plan a trip to do a physical activity (e.g., mountain hike, long bike ride), then create a training plan to prepare together.</solution>
		<solution id='57'>Plan to play an active game with your children (Wii, tag, kiddie yoga). </solution>
		<solution id='58'>Plan your exercise with a schedule. Write it in your calendar at the beginning of the week.</solution>
		<solution id='59'>Post on Facebook that you are looking for an exercise buddy.</solution>
		<solution id='60'>Put a dollar in a jar after each workout. Use the money toward a spa treatment, a new toy, or an outfit.</solution>
		<solution id='61'>Put a window air conditioner in the room you exercise in.</solution>
		<solution id='62'>Put bottles of water in the freezer to take with you on walks, rides, or runs.</solution>
		<solution id='63'>Put your exercise clothes and shoes on right when you get home from work to get in the mood</solution>
		<solution id='64'>Reduce alcohol intake to no more than 1 drink per day</solution>
		<solution id='65'>Remove electronics from your room at night.</solution>
		<solution id='66'>Replace naps with light physical activity.</solution>
		<solution id='67'>Research local gyms to find one that offers free or low-cost personal training</solution>
		<solution id='68'>Schedule exercise on the days you don't work. </solution>
		<solution id='69'>Schedule the days and times you will do your physical therapy exercises. </solution>
		<solution id='70'>Set a timer to get up and walk for 5 mins after sitting for 2 hours or more</solution>
		<solution id='71'>Set up fans near your home exercise equipment.</solution>
		<solution id='72'>Shovel snow for the amount of time you would normally workout.</solution>
		<solution id='73'>Sign up for a race that raises money for a cause you are both passionate about and follow a training plan to prepare together.</solution>
		<solution id='74'>Sign up for a race that raises money for a cause you are passionate about and follow a training plan to prepare.</solution>
		<solution id='75'>Start a Couch to 5K plan to have a goal to strive for.</solution> 
		<solution id='76'>Start a light exercise regimen (e.g., walking, yoga)</solution>
		<solution id='77'>Start by finding just one day that you can exercise over the next week for 10 minutes. </solution>
		<solution id='78'>Start with 10 minute workouts and gradually increase by 1 minute per week.</solution>
		<solution id='79'>Start with very light exercise that doesn't feel overwhelming or exhausting, e.g., leisurely walk, light yoga</solution>
		<solution id='80'>Stress may be making you feel exhausted, delegate a few key tasks that will open up some free time for you.</solution>
		<solution id='81'>Take an exercise class to have company while you exercise.</solution>
		<solution id='82'>Take an exercise class.</solution>
		<solution id='83'>Take your baby for daily walks outside or at the mall when the weather is bad.</solution>
		<solution id='84'>Talk to your doctor about your sleep.</solution>
		<solution id='85'>Talk to your doctor or a mental health professional about whether you might have depression.</solution>
		<solution id='86'>Tell your physician that your injury is preventing you from exercising. </solution>
		<solution id='87'>Try a 10 minute walk when you feel tired to see if it boosts your energy level.</solution>
		<solution id='88'>Try a completely different exercise.</solution>
		<solution id='89'>Try relaxation exercises before bedtime.</solution>
		<solution id='90'>Use a mobile app that offers personal training services</solution>
		<solution id='91'>Use an app like Nexercise, Gympact, or Charity Miles to earn rewards for your exercise</solution>
		<solution id='92'>Use an exercise app with a friend to keep each other accountable (e.g., MapMyWalk)</solution>
		<solution id='93'>Use the voice recorder on your phone to journal, record thoughts, or make lists while you workout</solution>
		<solution id='94'>Walk at the mall before it opens. </solution>
		<solution id='95'>Wear a cooling towel while you workout outside</solution>
		<solution id='96'>Wear a light baseball hat or visor to keep sun off of your face.</solution>
		<solution id='97'>Work with a personal trainer to identify exercises that work different body parts than the one that is injured.</solution>
		<solution id='98'>You mentioned that you own [equipment] pick one of these to use in the next week. </solution>
		<solution id='99'>You said you are interested in trying []selected option in profile 6]. Select one that you will try in the next week.</solution>
		<solution id='100'>You said you enjoy or want to try [winter sports], make plans to do these.</solution>
		<solution id='101'>You said you had [home exercise equipment], construct an indoor workout with these.</solution>
		<solution id='102'>You said you like these exercises [selected options] select one that you are willing to start this week.</solution>
		<solution id='103'>You said you were interested in trying these exercises [exercises], pick one to give a try this week.</solution>

	</solutions>

</script>